Guide to the H. Elliott McClure Papers, 1947-1989.
McClure, H. Elliott papers
- Series XI: Manuscripts and Drafts
  - English Vernacular Names of Birds of Malaysia (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Identification of Leaf Warblers in Thailand, by J. T. Marshall and S. Pantuwanta (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - What Can I Expect? (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Hornbills - Left Over Dinosaurs (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Manuscript, Photographs and Tables: Mosquito Associations in a Coastal Coconut-Nipah Palm Habitat (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - A Collection of Ectoparasites from Malayan Birds (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Arthropod Movements in the Strip-mine Area, Illinois, 1934-1935, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript, Data, Correspondence: Bats Over Bagkok, 1971-1978 (Box 28, Folder 66)
  - Conservation Contest Themes, Kuala Lumpur (Box 28, Folder 67)
  - Manuscript and Photographs: Birds in Religion (Box 28, Folder 68)
  - List of Manuscripts (Box 28, Folder 69)
- Series XII: Papers and Reprints
  - Thai Nature Clippings, 1974-1984 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Thai Nature Clippings and Others, 1985-1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Thai Nature Clippings, 1970-1973 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - San Diego Zoonooz; Paintings of Australian Birds, January - May 1967 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Birds of South East Asia, by Ben King (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Royal Selangor Club, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - The Thung Yai Hunting Scandal I, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - The Thung Yai Hunting Scandal II, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 59)
  - A Thai View of Americans, Standard Bangkok Magazine, February 1970 (Box 28, Folder 60)
- Series XIII: Publications and Reports: US Army
  - MAPS Annual Progress Report, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - MAPS Annual Progress Report, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Naval Medical Research Institute: Research Reports (1956, 1960, 1970); US NMR Unit 2: Outline of Current Research (1971); First international Seminar of SEATO Medical Research Laboratory (February 1971), 1956, 1960, 1969, 1970, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 65)